Guide to the Mann Library records, 1908-2011.
Mann Library records, 1908-2011
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Mann Library records, 1908-2011.
21-6-2748
Albert R. Mann Library.
43.2 cubic ft.
Correspondence, Diaries, Financial Records, Printed Materials, Publications, Reports.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Collection development records, vendor correspondence, and permanent records of the library of the New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences. Also old Mann Library plaque.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Collection development records, vendor correspondence, and permanent records of the library of the New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences. Also old Mann Library plaque.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Albert R. Mann Library.; Cornell University--Libraries.
Subjects:
Academic libraries--Administration.; Academic libraries--Statistics.; Library buildings.; Library finance.; Academic librarians.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
Includes collection #13-7-538.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Correspondence, general
Series II. Correspondence, Sam Demas Day Files
Series III. Correspondence, Jan Olsen Appointment Books and Day Files
Series IV. Budget
Series V. Meeting Minutes, Reports, and Statistics
Series VI. Building Projects
Series VII. Miscellaneous
Series VIII. Manuals
Series IX. Awards
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Correspondence, General
  - (Note: Some correspondence is included in Series V. Reports folders below.)
  - Correspondence "A", 1908-1915 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence "B", 1909-1915 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence "C", 1909-1919 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence "D", 1909-1915 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence "E", 1909-1915 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence "F", 1908-1915 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence "G", 1908-1915 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence "H", 1908-1915 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence "I-J", 1908-1913 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence "K", 1908-1913 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence "L", 1911-1915 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence "M", 1911-1915 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence "N", 1909-1915 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence "O", 1909-1913 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence "P-Q", 1908-1915 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence "R", 1908-1915 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence "S", 1909-1915 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence "T-U", 1908-1915 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence "V", 1909-1915 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence "W-Z", 1908-1915 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence concerning missing books, 1915-1919 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence concerning periodicals list, 1916 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence concerning Agricultural Library - Memorandum, 1916 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence concerning bindery recods (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence concerning book lists, 1888-1912 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1910-1911 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1911-1912 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1912-1913 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence "A-L", 1913-1914 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence "M-Z", 1913-1914 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 1914-1915 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1915-1916 (Box 36, Folder 19-21)
  - Correspondence-Library Committee, 1915-1916 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence-Library Committee, 1910-1914 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence-Library Committee, 1914-1915 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence-Library Committee, 1910-1911 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence and Reports-Library Committee, 1911-1912 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence-Library Committee, 1912-1913 (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence-Library Committee, 1913-1914 (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence-Library, 1915-1916 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence-Library Committee, 1916-1917 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence-Library Committee, 1917-1919 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence "A", 1916-1918 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence "A", 1918-1919 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence "B", 1916-1919 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence "C", 1916-1919 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence "D", 1916-1919 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence - Director's, 1910-1919 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence "E", 1917-1919 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence "F", 1916-1919 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence "G", 1916-1919 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence "H", 1916-1919 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence "I", 1916-1919 (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence "J", 1917-1920 (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence "K", 1916-1919 (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence "L", 1910-1919 (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence "M", 1916-1917 (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence "M", 1918-1919 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence "O", 1916-1917 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence "P", 1916-1919 (Box 33, Folder 3-4)
  - Correspondence "R", 1916-1919 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence "S", 1916-1917 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence "S", 1918-1919 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence-Stechert, G.E., 1916-1919 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence "T", 1916-1919 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence "U", 1916-1919 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence-United States, 1916-1919 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence-private, 1917-1919 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence-University Library, 1916-1919 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence-Receipts, Lists of missing library books, 1917-1919 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence "V", 1916-1919 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence "W", 1916-1919 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence "X-Z", 1917-1918 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence- "A", July 1922-July 1925 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence- "B", 1922-07-1925-07 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence- "C", 1922-07-1925-07 (Box 39, Folder 5-6)
  - Correspondence- "D", 1922-07-1925-07 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence-Dean of the College of Agriculture, 1922-07-1925-07 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence- "E", 1922-07-1925-07 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence- "F", 1922-07-1925-07 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence-Faculty, 1922-07-1925-07 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence- "G", 1922-07-1925-07 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence- "H", 1922-07-1925-07 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence- "I", 1922-07-1925-07 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence- "J", 1922-07-1925-07 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence- "K", 1922-07-1925-07 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence- "L", 1922-07-1925-07 (Box 39, Folder 17-18)
  - Correspondence- "M", 1923-07-1925-07 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence- "N", 1923-07-1925-07 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence- "O", 1923-07-1924-07 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence- "P", 1923-06-1925-01 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence- "Q", 1923-03-1925-04 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence- "R", 1923-07-1925-05 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence-Sherman, John D., 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence- "S", 1923-1925 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence- Stechert, G.E., 1923-1925 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence- "T", 1923-1925 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence- "U", 1922-1924 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence-University, 1922-1925 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence-University Library, 1924-1925 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence- "V", 1923-1924 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence- "W", 1921-1925 (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence- "X-Z", 1924 (Box 39, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence-Library, Borrowings, A-H, 1928-1929 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence-Library, Borrowings,I-O, 1918-1929 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence-Library, Borrowings,P-Z, 1928-1929 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence-Library, Borrowings,A-H, 1929-1930 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence-Library, Borrowings,I-O, 1929-1930 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence-Library, Borrowings,P-Z, 1929-1930 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence- "A", 1928-1929 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence-Agriculture, 1928-1929 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence- "B", 1928-1929 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence- "C", 1928-1929 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence-Catalog, 1926-1928 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence-College Stores, 1928-1929 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence-Cornell University Library, 1928-1929 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence- "D", 1928-1929 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence-Dean, 1928-1929 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence- "E", 1928-1929 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence-Entomololgy, 1928-1929 (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence - "F", 1928-1929 (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence-Faculty, 1928-1929 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence-Forestry, 1928-1929 (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence- "G", 1928-1929 (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence- "H, 1928-1929 (Box 33, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence-Home Economics, 1928-1929 (Box 33, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence- "I", 1928-1929 (Box 33, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence- "J", 1928-1929 (Box 33, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence - "K", 1928-1929 (Box 33, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence- "L", 1928-1929 (Box 33, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence-Library of Congress, 1928-1929 (Box 33, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence, Library-USDA, 1928-1929 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence- "M", 1928-1929 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence-Mutual Library Bindery, 1928-1929 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence- "N", 1928-1929 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence-New York State Experiment Station, 1928-1929 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, "O", 1928-1929 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence- "P", 1928-1929 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - Plant Pathology, 1928-1929 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence- "R", 1928-1929 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence -Rural Education, Rural Engineering, Rural Social Organization, 1928-1929 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence- "S", 1928-1929 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence-Stechert, 1928-1929 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence-Board of Supervisors, 1928-1929 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence - Superintendent of Documents, 1928-1929 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence- "T", 1928-1929 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence- "U", 1928-1929 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence-U.S. Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence - "V", 1928-1929 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence- "W", 1928-1929 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence-Weigel, 1928-1929 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence- "X-Z", 1928-1929 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence- "A", 1929-1930 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence- "B", 1929-1930 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence- "C", 1929-1930 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence-College Stores, 1929-1930 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence-Cornell Library, 1929-1930 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence- "D", 1929-1930 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence-Dean, 1929-1930 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence- "E", 1929-1930 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence- "F", 1929-1930 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence-Faculty, 1929-1930 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence-Fedde, 1929-1930 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence- "G", 1929-1930 (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence- "H", 1929-1930 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence- "I", 1929-1930 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence- "J", 1929-1930 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence- "K", 1929-1930 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence- "L", 1929-1930 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence- "M", 1929-1930 (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence- "N", 1929-1930 (Box 34, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence-NYAES, 1929-1930 (Box 34, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence- "O", 1929-1930 (Box 34, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence- "P", 1929-1930 (Box 34, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence- "R", 1929-1930 (Box 34, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence- "S", 1929-1930 (Box 34, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence- "U-V", 1929-1930 (Box 34, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence- "W", 1929-1930 (Box 34, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence-Wilson, H.W., 1930-1931 (Box 34, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence- "X-Z", 1929-1930 (Box 34, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence- "A", 1930-1931 (Box 34, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence- "B", 1930-1931 (Box 34, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence-Business Office, 1929-1931 (Box 34, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence- "C", 1930-1931 (Box 34, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence-College Stores, 1930-1931 (Box 34, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence-Cornell University Library, 1930-1931 (Box 34, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence- "D", 1930-1931 (Box 34, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence-Dairy, 1930-1931 (Box 34, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence-Dean, 1930-1931 (Box 34, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence- "E", 1930-1931 (Box 34, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence- "F", 1930-1931 (Box 34, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence-Faculty, 1930-1931 (Box 34, Folder 61)
  - Correspondence- "G", 1930-1931 (Box 34, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence- "H", 1930-1931 (Box 34, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence- "I", 1930-1931 (Box 34, Folder 64)
  - Correspondence- "J", 1930-1931 (Box 34, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence- "K", 1930-1931 (Box 34, Folder 66)
  - Correspondence- "L", 1930-1931 (Box 34, Folder 67)
  - Correspondence-Library of Congress, 1929-1930 (Box 34, Folder 68)
  - Correspondence-Libray-USDA, 1929-1930 (Box 34, Folder 69)
  - Correspondence- "M", 1930-1931 (Box 34, Folder 70)
  - Correspondence-Mutual Library Bindery, 1930-1931 (Box 34, Folder 71)
  - Correspondence- "N", 1930-1931 (Box 34, Folder 72)
  - Correspondence- "O", 1930-1931 (Box 34, Folder 73)
  - Correspondence- "P", 1930-1931 (Box 34, Folder 74)
  - Correspondence-Purchasing Dept., 1930-1931 (Box 34, Folder 75)
  - Correspondence- "R", 1930-1931 (Box 34, Folder 76)
  - Correspondence-Secretary and Treasurer, 1936-1940 (Box 34, Folder 77)
  - Correspondence-Stechert, G.E., 1929-1930 (Box 34, Folder 78)
  - Correspondence-Stechert, G.E., 1930-1931 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence-Superintendent of Documents, 1930-1931 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence- "T", 1930-1931 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence-Wilson, H.W., 1930-1932 (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence-Applications, 1935-1936 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence-Business Office, 1935-1940 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence-Cornell University Library, 1935-1940 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence- "A", 1935-1940 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence- "B", 1935-1940 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence- "C", 1935-1940 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence- "D", 1935-1940 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence- Dean, 1935-1940 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence- "E", 1935-1940 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence- "F", 1935-1940 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence- Faculty, 1935-1940 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence- "G", 1935-1940 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence- "H", 1935-1940 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence- "I", 1935-1940 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence- "J", 1935-1940 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence- "K", 1935-1940 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence- "L", 1935-1940 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence- "M", 1935-1940 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence- "N", 1935-1940 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence-National Youth Administration-Student Aid Program, 1935-1936 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence-National Youth Administration-Student Aid Program, 1936-1937 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence-National Youth Administration-Student Aid Program, 1937-1938 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence-National Youth Administration-Student Aid Program, 1938-1939 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence-National Youth Administration-Student Aid Program, 1939-1940 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence- "O", 1935-1940 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence- "P", 1935-1940 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence-Purchasing Dept., 1936-1940 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence- "Q", 1939-1940 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence- "R", 1935-1940 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence- "S", 1935-1940 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence-Stechert, G.E., 1935-1936 (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence-Stechert, G.E., 1936-1937 (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence-Stechert, G.E., 1937-1938 (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence-Stechert, G.E., 1938-1939 (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence - Stechert, G.E., 1939-1940 (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence-Superintendent of Documents, 1935-1939 (Box 35, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence- "T", 1935-1940 (Box 35, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence- "U", 1935-1940 (Box 35, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence- "V", 1935-1940 (Box 35, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence- "W", 1935-1940 (Box 35, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence-Wilson, H.W., 1935-1940 (Box 35, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence- "X,Y,Z", 1935-1940 (Box 35, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence-Library Committee "A-F", 1945-1946 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence-Library Committee "G-L", 1945-1946 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence- Library Committee "Mc-R", 1945-1946 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence-Library Committee "S-Z", 1945-1946 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence-Library Committee, 1947-1948 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Library Memos, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence-Campus "A-B", 1947-1948 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence-Campus "C", 1947-1948 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence- Campus "D-H", 1947-1948 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence-Campus "I-K", 1947-1948 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence-Campus "L", 1947-1948 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence-Campus "M", 1947-1948 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence-Campus "N-S", 1947-1948 (Box 37, Folder 28-29)
  - Correspondence-Campus T-Z", 1946-1948 (Box 38, Folder 1-2)
  - Correspondence-Departmental, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence-Departments "A-F", 1944-1946 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence-Departments "G-Z", 1944-1946 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence-F.W.Faxon and Company, 1916-1930 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence-Bookbinding, 1948-1949 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence-W.Junk, 1928-1929 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence-List of Books, 1916-1948 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence-Multiple Dealers, 1947-1948 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Off-Campus Correspondence- "A", 1947-1948 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Off-Campus Correspondence- "B", 1947-1948 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Off-Campus Correspondence- "C-D", 1947-1948 (Box 38, Folder 13-14)
  - Off-Campus Correspondence- "E-F", 1947-1948 (Box 38, Folder 15-16)
  - Off-Campus Correspondence- "G-H", 1947-1948 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Off-Campus Correspondence- "I", 1947-1948 (Box 38, Folder 18-19)
  - Off-Campus Correspondence- "J", 1947-1948 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Off-Campus Correspondence- "K", 1947-1948 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Off-Campus Correspondence- "L-M", 1947-1948 (Box 38, Folder 22-23)
  - Off-Campus Correspondence- "N-O", 1947-1948 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Off-Campus Correspondence- "P-R", 1947-1948 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Off-Campus Correspondence- "S", 1947-1948 (Box 38, Folder 26-27)
  - Off-Campus Correspondence-Stechert-Hafner, 1947-1948 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Off-Campus Correspondence- "T-V", 1947-1948 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Off-Campus Correspondence- "T-V", 1947-1948 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Off-Campus Correspondence- "W", 1947-1948 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence- "A-Am", 1946-1952 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence- "An-Az", 1947-1952 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence-Abrahams, 1948-1952 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence- "B", 1946-1952 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence- "C", 1947-1952 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence- "D", 1948-1952 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence- "E", 1947-1952 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence- "F", 1947-1952 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence-F.W. Foxon Company, 1947-1952 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence- "G", 1947-1951 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence- "H", 1947-1952 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence- "I", 1947-1952 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence- "J", 1947-1952 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence- "K", 1947-1951 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence- "L", 1947-1952 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence- "M", 1949-1952 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence- "N", 1948-1952 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence- "O", 1948-1951 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence- "P", 1948-1952 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence- "Q", 1947-1952 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence- "R", 1947-1952 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence-Ridley Bindery Lists, 1951-1952 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence- "S", 1949-1952 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence- "T", 1950-1952 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence- "U", 1948-1952 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence- "V", 1947-1950 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence- "W", 1947-1952 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence-Wilson, H.W., 1947-1952 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence-States-Services, 1946 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence-States-A-H, 1946 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence-States-I-N, 1946-1947 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence-States-New York, 1944-1948 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence-States-New York-Department of Agricultural Economics, 1945-1947 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence-States-New York-Department of Agricultural Economics, 1944-1950 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence-States-New York-Department of Audit and Control, 1945-1951 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence-States-New York-Department of Farms and Markets, 1924 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence-States-New York-Department of Labor, 1939-1945 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence-States-New York-Department of Social Welfard, 1941-1943 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence-States-New York-Department of State, 1927-1948 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence-States-New York-Department of Taxation and Finance, 1932-1948 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence-States-New York-Public Service Commission, 1931 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence-States-O-R, 1944-1945 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence-States-S-Z, 1944-1945 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence-States-Puerto Rico, 1938-1952 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence-Territories and Possessions-United States-Agricultural Economics, 1946-1947 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence-Territories and Possessions-United States-Agricultural Marketing, 1942 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence-Territories and Possessions-United States-Agriculture, 1937-1949 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence-Territories and Possessions-United States-Agriculture Production and Marketing Administration, 1946 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence-Territories and Possessions-United States-Executive Order 9809, 1946-1948 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence-Territories and Possessions-United States-Executive Order-House, 1944-1950 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence-Territories and Possessions-United States-Executive Order-Senate, 1948 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence-Territories and Possessions-United States-Experiment Stations, 1947 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence-Territories and Possessions-United States-Farm Credit Administration, 1943-1950 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence-Territories and Possessions-United States-Farm Security Administration, 1945 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence-Territories and Possessions-United States-Federal Reserve Board, 1933-1946 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence-Territories and Possessions-United States-Federal Surplus Commodities Corp., 1945 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence-Territories and Possessions-United States-Federal Trade Commission, 1938-1946 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence-Territories and Possessions-United States-Food Distribution Administration, 1943-1947 (Box 40, Folder 30)